sensation.com 2003-02-05

# Terms

http://www.sensation.com   
Sensation has created this Privacy Policy Statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your personal privacy and the principles of informed consent. 

Please read all sections of this Privacy Policy Statement, as they explain fully:   
1\. What are Sensation.com and Sensation Direct?  
2\. How will Sensation Direct modify my computer?  
3\. Why information is collected?  
4\. When and how information is collected?  
5\. What information is collected?  
6\. How information is used?  
7\. What choices you have regarding the collection and use of information?  
8\. What security measures are taken by Sensation?

WHAT IS Sensation.COM AND Sensation DIRECT?   
Sensation.com is a subscription-based entertainment portal that allows users to purchase and view movies on their computer. Sensation Direct is a software application that allows users to easily download, and install software and other files from the Internet. 

HOW WILL Sensation DIRECT MODIFY MY COMPUTER?   
WARNING: Sensation DIRECT WILL MAKE THE FOLLOWING CHANGES TO YOUR INTERNET BROWSER AND COMPUTER. THESE CHANGES WILL OCCUR OVER TIME AS THESE FEATURES ARE DOWNLOADED TO YOUR COMPUTER. "SOFTWARE CONFLICTS" may occur with other browser-based software applications that may already be installed on your computer. Sensation Direct will overwrite these applications to resolve these conflicts whenever possible. 

"AUTO UPDATE" is a feature used by Sensation Direct to ensure that you have the most recently released version of the Sensation Direct software. Once you have installed the software, Sensation Direct will make periodic requests to keep the software updated. 

"THIRD-PARTY SOFTWARE APPLICATIONS may be bundled with Sensation Direct. These applications have their own terms and conditions and privacy policies. Sensation provides links to these documents. 

BY ACCEPTING THE CHANGES OUTLINED ABOVE YOU WILL BE GIVEN FREE ACCESS TO ENTERTAINMENT RELATED CONTENT (CELEBRITY EVENTS, PHOTO GALLERIES, MOVIES, VIDEO PLAYERS, ENCODERS) THAT WILL BE DOWNLOADED TO YOUR COMPUTER. 

WHY IS INFORMATION COLLECTED?   
Anonymous demographic information is collected for the purposes of delivering marketing messages to end-users that better match their interests and profile. 

If you visit our Web site http://www.sensation.com, Sensation and its licensor may collect and store only the following nonpersonally-identifying information from you: the name of the domain name from which you access the Internet (e.g., aol.com, if you are connecting from an America OnlineTM account); the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our Web site and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. 

Personally identifying information we collect and store about you is the information you choose to provide to us when you register to Sensation.com, purchase items at Sensation.com, or install Sensation Direct. Sensation registration process may require users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company, promotional material from some of our partners, and third parties. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Sensation DOES NOT COLLECT ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13. 

WHEN AND HOW IS INFORMATION COLLECTED?   
Upon installation of Sensation Direct, your computer is assigned a unique numerical identifier. This unique identifier allows Sensation' and its licensors’ servers to measure and report aggregate information (such as the number of people who read an advertisement, or the number of times an advertisement is seen) to advertisers. It also allows Sensation to collect information regarding your own use of, and interaction with advertising so that we can deliver advertising content that is more relevant to your own particular wants and needs, and avoid subjecting you to overly repetitive ads. 

Cookies   
Sensation may also use "cookie" technology to monitor user activity on the Sensation Web site. A "cookie" is a small amount of data that is created by a Web server and stored on your local hard drive upon your first visit to a Web site. Cookies identify you to, and can be accessed only by the Web server that assigned the cookie. Cookies streamline and personalize your Web browsing experience by storing passwords, purchases, and personal preferences like Web page layouts, Web content, stock symbols, etc., so that you do not have to reenter this information every time you visit a particular Web page. 

Technology from Sensation Direct resides on your local system and operates in the background, dynamically collecting and transmitting volunteered anonymous demographic information and volunteered personally identifying information about you, while Sensation Direct is active on your system. The demographic information collected and transmitted may also include information about your operating system, Internet Protocol Address, and Internet service provider (ISP). 

WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?   
Anonymous demographic information collected by Sensation may include, but is not limited to, your: (a) gender; (b) age; (c) zip code; (d) operating system; (e) Internet protocol address. Such demographic information may be collected whenever you provide it to Sensation, or to other third parties while interacting with the application. Information such as (a) what advertising messages you have seen in Sensation; (b) what advertising messages you have clicked on inside Sensation; (c) how many advertisements you have viewed inside Sensation may be collected at any time, even if Sensation is not active. 

WHAT PERSONALLY INDENTIFYING INFORMATION IS COLLECTED?   
Personally identifying information collected by Sensation may include, but is not limited to, your: (a) first and last name; (b) home or other physical address including street name and number, and name of city or town; (c) email address, and; (d) telephone number (e) credit card or other financial information. Such personally identifying information is collected only when you VOLUNTARILY provide it to Sensation, or voluntarily enter it into "pop-up windows" generated by Sensation. 

HOW IS INFORMATION USED?   
The demographic and personally identifying information collected by Sensation may be maintained separately and/or combined to create user profiles. The demographic and personally identifying information, and/or the user profiles may also be supplemented by information derived from third-party information vendors. The demographic and personally identifying information collected by Sensation, and/or the user profiles, may be used by Sensation, its licensees, licensors, agents, and assigns, and/or its client software companies and developers, as well as shared, rented, leased, sold, or otherwise made available to third-party marketing entities, advertisers, and other parties and entities, at the sole discretion of Sensation. Some of Sensation 's clients may use the demographic and personally identifying information to personalize Web pages and target ads, products and services to consumers. 

WHAT CHOICES DO YOU HAVE, AS A USER, REGARDING THE COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION? 

Disabling Cookies   
If you do not wish Sensation.com or Sensation Direct to monitor your activity or you choose not to access, correct or update your demographic or personally identifying information on the Sensation.com Web site, you may choose to disable your Web browser's (Netscape Communicator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, etc.) ability to accept cookies. You may do so by: (1) following the directions provided with your Web browser; (2) managing the contents of the cookies.txt file directly, or; (3) by using 3rd party cookie management tools. Please note that disabling cookies may be a complicated task, and is not recommended for novice PC users. 

Un-install   
If, after installing, using, or copying Sensation Direct, you decide that you no longer wish to share your demographic or personally identifying information, you may perform a complete un-installation of Sensation Direct. This can be accomplished by using the add/remove function within your “control panel.” 

Completely un-installing any and all products incorporating Sensation Direct technology will prevent the Sensation Direct technology from collecting and transmitting any personally identifying or demographic information about you and your use of the Internet, etc., to Sensation. It will not, however, prevent Sensation from sharing, renting, leasing, selling, or otherwise making available to third-party marketing or other entities, at the sole discretion of Sensation, the demographic, personally identifying, and user profile information that has already been collected. 

What if the Privacy Policy Changes?   
By installing, using, or copying Sensation Direct you acknowledge that you have read, understood, given your informed consent to, and agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement. You must, generally, therefore, perform a complete un-installation of Sensation Direct Technology (as described above) in order to prevent Sensation ' collection of demographic, personally identifying, and user profile information. 

* Exception. If the terms of this are revised, this Privacy Policy Statement is subject to change by "Sensation" at any time. Notice to members shall be made by adding any changes to this " Privacy Policy Statement " document, which will remain posted at the Site. Members agree to review these " Privacy Policy Statement " from time to time for changes and updates. Notice of any revisions to this Privacy Policy Statement shall be considered effective when transmitted to the Sensation.com servers. 

SECURITY   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All information is for our accounting and registration purposes only. Only authorized employees of Sensation will have access to this information. 

THIRD PARTY PRIVACY   
Please be aware that Sensation.com and Sensation Direct advertisers or Web sites that have links in software on our network may collect personally identifying information about you. This Privacy Policy Statement does not cover the information practices of those Web sites linking information about Sensation. Sensation does not have any responsibility or liability for any information, contents, communications or materials available on such third-party sites. 

From time to time, Sensation works with third-party ad servers to serve advertising to Sensation users. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize unique "cookies" on your browser and may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this and other Web sites about goods and services of interest to you. 

NOTICE: If, after installing, using, or copying the product, you decide that you prefer to discontinue disclosing your personally identifying and/or demographic information, you may perform a complete un-installation of the product and any and all products incorporating the licensed software. You may not, however, disable the licensed software and continue to use this or any product that incorporates the licensed software.
